nop-templates.com 2015-12-06

# Nop-Templates.com Privacy Information

We, at Nop-Templates.com, respect your privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information you share with us. This policy explains our online information practices for protecting and using your information.  
 **This privacy policy applies exclusively to the Nop-Templates.com web site. It does not apply to the practices of companies that SevenSpikes Ltd does not own or control, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Nop-Templates.com links.**

**Collecting and Use Of Information**

You can visit and view Nop-Templates.com without revealing any personal information. However, if you want to purchase a template, extension or service, signup for our newsletter or use certain nop-templates services, we will need some personal information.  
Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. Nop-Templates.com will use this information to issue an invoice, to provide you with requested products and services, to contact you regarding new products and services, for processing your orders, answering your inquiries, providing you with access to special information and offers, or for rendering special services. We will not provide your personal data to other third parties without your express permission and, above all, we will not sell this data to anyone or make it available in any other form.  
We will collect general information (such as the IP address assigned to you by your Internet service provider, information about the Internet Browser you are using, the web site from which you are visiting us and which of our web pages you visit, including the date and time of each visit) to improve our website and better meet your needs. These data is absolutely anonymous and cannot be associated with an individual person.

**Cookies**

On some of our web pages, we use cookies to monitor the preferences of our visitors so that we can tailor our web sites accordingly. A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps your browsing experience. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. You may block cookies, or delete existing cookies, by adjusting the appropriate setting on your browser. Please consult the HELP menu of your browser to learn how to do this

**Data Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We use appropriate technical and organizational means to protect your data against misuse, loss, damage or unauthorized access, change and deletion. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. Our security measures are constantly tested and improved in accordance with our technical and organizational capabilities.
